Alain Jeshua Melendez Diaz

Developer +54 9 11 2797-9080 alainjeshua@gmail.com





Professional Profile

I am an enthusiastic and productive person. I like the teamwork in an honest environment and with effective communication. I have a good resolution capacity, contributing ideas to projects and above all being focused on the objectives set and delivery dates.

Even though my years of experience are focused on other areas, if those are articulated with programming knowledge, I am ready to face the challenge of my first work experience as a Programmer.

Work Experience

2022 - Current	Full-Stack Developer. GoCode
2017 - 2022	Others. Customer service, administrative assistant, store cashier

Education

2020 - Current	Programming Studies in Udemy – Global Mentoring (Python, PostgreSQL, JSON, Tkinter, HTML, CSS)
2021 - 2022	Specialized Program Learn to code with Python. Universidad Austral. Buenos Aires, Argentina
2006 - 2013	Bachelor in Education, Universidad Central de Venezuela (9no Semestre)
1998 - 2003	High School Diploma, Unidad Educativa Instituto "La Salle", Venezuela

Languages

- Spanish (Native)
- English (Intermediate Reading and Writing)